g-boxnetwork.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy policy of web hosting services

**In an effort to protect our clients' and site visitors privacy and rights, 000webhost.Com has established a Privacy Policy which explains what information we gather on visitors and what we do with information that we gather.

We advise all visitors and clients to read and understand our privacy policy, and to check it periodically for any updates or revisions. If you have any questions about the contents of our statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mailing: contact@000webhost.com

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which 000webhost.Com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User"). 

**

### Privacy

Users' privacy is very important to 000webhost.Com. 000webhost.Com is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to 000webhost.Com.

### The Information We Collect

000webhost.Com collects personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. 000webhost.Com may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users’ PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.

### How We Use Information

000webhost.Com may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by 000webhost.Com and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with 000webhost.Com and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. 000webhost.Com may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of 000webhost.Com, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. At no time will 000webhost.Com's database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists.

### Disclosure of Information

000webhost.Com may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of 000webhost.Com's business.

### Maintenance of Information

Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

### Recaptcha

We use third party software called “Google Recaptcha” that collects information about users for security reasons.

Information collected by reCAPTCHA is held in accordance with the Google Privacy Policy.

### Questions

Users may direct questions concerning this statement by e-mail to: contact@000webhost.com. Users may elect not to receive solicitations from 000webhost.Com or from trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners by letting us know.
